rightbackup.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Right Backup

---  
  
Privacy Policy

Rightbackup.com is strongly committed to protect your privacy and provide a safe online experience for all of our users and registered customers while offering the highest quality products and services to them. We may gather certain types of information about and from you to fulfill your request and serve your needs better, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions covering the collection and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we may gather, how we may use it and how to correct or change it.

Please read the "Privacy Policy" completely, as well as our 'Terms and Conditions' for use of information we may gather. Should you have any questions in this regard, feel free to contact us.

What Information we may collect about you?

You can visit our website, read products description and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. Since we provide our customers and newsletter subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service; we may request information about you under occasional circumstances. For your convenience and to serve you better, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have, however, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving newsletter and other information from us.

We collect personally identifiable information; such as name, mailing address and e-mail address when you register to one of our products or place an order (see the section below for more information on placing order). Website visitors may register to receive our newsletter by submitting their name and e-mail address.

  * Placing Orders

If you wish to place an order for our products, you can generally enter the requisite details. In addition to the customary information that may be required to fill your order (full name, address, phone number, ship-to name and address etc.), collection of additional information such as your credit card number and credit card expiration date, is dependent on option of payment as we offer online and offline subscribers additional options such as check, money order and credit card order by fax or phone.

What we may do with the information we collect?

We use information you provide to fulfill your request and improve our products and services. We may use personal information to display or send personalized content to our website visitors as well as to send newsletter, product features, promotional material, special offers and other updates to our customers and newsletter subscribers. A subscriber may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, resolve customers’ issues like respond to any problems that may arise such as product delivery failures, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products are most popular with users.

We allow users of our website to email us their queries. We do not retain any email address (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such e-mail or links after they are sent.

How do we share Personal Information?

We may share your personal information with the parties described below:

  * Credit Card Companies:

As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the affiliate, products purchased, date and total cost. RightBackup.com will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company.

  * Payment Gateways:

Credit card numbers are only shared with our partners with whom you place an online order. They process the billing of such products on our behalf.Rest assured that we and our payment gateways follow careful procedures to safeguard credit card data in connection with your transactions.

  * Important Note:

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

How do we use cookies?

Your Web browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify your personal details. Cookies assist us in ascertaining which of our products you like best. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. Our website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser.

Links

Rightbackup.com may offer links to or from websites it controls to other sites. We offer links to some renowned websites that review and rate our products and market them so that you can be conversant on authenticity of products performance.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update "Privacy Policy" as necessary to protect you to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand the prevailing policy. If we make material changes to this policy we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we may handle any of your previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered customers and newsletter subscribers information on material changes to this policy.
